Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
- Program recordings
  - 181. Paris in the Thirties: Bill Coleman and Django Reinhardt, Mehling, Paul
    With guest Paul Mehling of the Hot Club of San Francisco. Recorded live at the Stanford Jazz workshop. See also Stanford recordings.
    Coleman, Bill, 1904-1981; Reinhardt, Django, 1910-1953; Stanford Jazz Workshop.
    - Paris in the Thirties: Mix 2, 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Paris in the Thirties. #45, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Paris in the Thirties. #22, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Paris in the Thirties. #33, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 182. Early Chart Toppers: Pop Hits of the 20th Century, Allen, Rex; Bagneris, Vernel; Ferro, Nina; Hopkins, Linda, 1924-; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Ogilvie, Brian; Peplowski, Ken; Vaché, Allan; Woods, Carol
    with guests Rex Allen, Dick Hyman, Vernel Bagneris, Brian Ogilvie, Ken Peplowski, Rebecca Kilgore, Allan Vaché, Nina Ferro, Carol Woods, and Linda Hopkins.
    - Chart Toppers Open Mix And All Elements, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 87)
    - Early Chart Toppers, 2001; 2 DATs (Audio 37)
      #47, 2001; Safety 2001
    - Early Chart Toppers. #47, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 183. Amazing Grace: A Program of Spirituals and Hymns, First United Methodist Church (Houston, Tex.). Choir.; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Dick Hyman and the First United Methodist Church Choir under the direction of Ken Axelson. Recorded live at the First United Methodist Church in Houston, Texas.
    Hymns; Spirituals (Songs)
    - Amazing Grace; Star Spangled Banner Malcolm Harper Remix, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Amazing Grace, 2001-2002; 3 DATs (Audio 38, Audio 37)
      #48, 2001; #47, 2002
    - Amazing Grace. #48, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Amazing Grace. #47, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Amazing Grace. #47, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 184. Beau Koo Jack: The Life and Music of Composer Alex Hill, Hal Smith's Roadrunners.; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-
    With guest band Hal Smith's Roadrunners with Rebecca Kilgore.
    Hill, Alex, 1906-1937
    - Beau Koo Jack. #50, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 185. Peck's Bad Boys: East Texas Jazz in the 20s, Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guest Dick Hyman. Live from the First United Methodist Church in Houston, Texas. Title changed for 2009 rebroadcast to "Peck's Bad Boys: The Peck Kelly Story."
    Kelley, Peck; Peck's Bad Boys.
    - Peck's Bad Boys, 2001-2003; 3 DATs (Audio 37, Audio 39)
      #51, 2001; Safety 2001; #1, 2003
    - Peck's Bad Boys. #51, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Peck's Bad Boys. #1, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Peck's Bad Boys. #40, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Peck's Bad Boys: The Peck Kelly Story. #20, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 186. Fireside New Year's Eve, Allen, Rex; Caceres, David; Cusack, Kim; Ferro, Nina; Gordon, Bobby; Havens, Bob; Ogilvie, Brian; Peplowski, Ken
    With guests Brian Ogilvie, Ken Peplowski, Rex Allen, Nina Ferro, David Caceres, Bob Havens, Kim Cusack, and Bobby Gordon. Title changed for 2001 rebroadcast to "Fireside Concert for the New Year."
    - Fireside New Year's Eve, 2001; 2 DATs (Audio 37)
      #52 2001; Safety 2001
    - Fireside New Year's Eve. #53 (KQED Master), 2004-12-30; 1 CD-R (Audio 89)
    - Fireside Concert for the New Year, With Special Guests. #52, 2001; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Fireside New Year's Eve. #53, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 187. Goody Goody: Love Songs to Mend a Broken Heart, Bagneris, Vernel; Burrell, Terry; Ferro, Nina; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kellso, Jon-Erik; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Payton, Nicholas; Woods, Carol
    With vocalists Rebecca Kilgore, Carol Woods, Nina Ferro, Vernel Bagneris, Topsy Chapman, and Terry Burrell; trumpeters Nicholas Payton and Jon-Erik Kellso; and pianist Dick Hyman.
    - Goody Goody. #2 Safety, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 37)
    - Goody Goody. #2, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 188. Soulmates of Song: Famous Jazz Partners, Chapman, Topsy; Ferro, Nina; Haggart, Bob; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Lawson, Yank; Mehling, Paul; Oakley, Leon; Stein, Andy; Walbridge, Mike; Woods, Carol
    with guests Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Andy Stein, Topsy Chapman, Nina Ferro, Paul Mehling, Rebecca Kilgore, Carol Woods, Dick Hyman, Yank Lawson, and Bob Haggart.
    - Soulmates of Song, 2002; 2 DATs (Audio 37)
      #4, 2002; Safety 2002
    - Soulmates of Song. #4, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 189. W.C., James P., and Bessie: The Geography of Jazz, Chapman, Topsy; Hopkins, Linda, 1924-; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Topsy Chapman, Linda Hopkins and Dick Hyman.
    Handy, W. C. (William Christopher), 1873-1958; Johnson, James P. (James Price), 1894-1955; Smith, Bessie, 1894-1937
    - Geography of Jazz Promos, 3 CD-Rs (Audio 87)
    - W.C., James P., and Bessie: Mix 2, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 89)
    - W.C., James P., and Bessie. #7 Safety, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 37)
    - W.C., James P., and Bessie. #7, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - W.C., James P., and Bessie. #41, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 190. Metropolis: Ode to New York City in the Twenties, Carter, Benny; Ferro, Nina; Gordon, Bobby; Grosz, Marty; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Stein, Andy; Vaché, Allan
    Guests include Dick Hyman, Benny Carter, Marty Grosz, Andy Stein, Nina Ferro, Bobby Gordon and Allan Vaché.
    - Metropolis. #9, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 37)
    - Metropolis. #9, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Metropolis. #38, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 191. Gumbo Ya-Ya: Creole Customs and Folklore, Bagneris, Vernel; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon
    With guests Vernel Bagneris, Leon Oakley and Dick Hyman.
    - Gumbo Ya-Ya Vernell Voice Tracks, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Gumbo Ya-Ya. #11 Safety, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Gumbo Ya-Ya. #11, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Gumbo Ya-Ya. #18, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 192. The Swing Shift: Jazz on Late Night Radio, Barrett, Dan; Cocuzzi, John; Havens, Bob; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Allan Vaché, John Cocuzzi, Rebecca Kilgore, Dan Barrett and Bob Havens.
    - Swing Shift. #14 Safety, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Swing Shift. #14, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Swing Shift. #39, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Swing Shift. #44, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 193. The World on Seven Strings: The Life of Jazz Guitar Master Bucky Pizzarelli, Pizzarelli, Bucky; Pizzarelli, John
    With guests Bucky and John Pizzarelli.
    Pizzarelli, Bucky
    - World on Seven Strings. #17, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - World on Seven Strings. #27, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - World on Seven Strings. #21, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - World on Seven Strings. #3, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 194. Sentimental Reasons: The Story of Nat King Cole with John Pizzarelli, Pizzarelli, Bucky; Pizzarelli, John
    With guests John Pizzarelli and Bucky Pizzarelli.
    Cole, Nat King, 1917-1965
    - Sentimental Reasons. #19, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Sentimental Reasons. #19, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Sentimental Reasons. #16, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Sentimental Reasons. #12, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Sentimental Reasons. #52, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 195. Flying Solo: A Jazz Concert for One, Capobianco, John; Galloway, Jim; Haggart, Bob; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Lawson, Yank; Oakley, Leon; Ogilvie, Brian; Smith, Hal, drummer; Vaché, Allan
    With guests John Capobianco, Allan Vaché, Brian Ogilvie, Dick Hyman, Leon Oakley, Yank Lawson, Bob Haggart, Hal Smith, and Jim Galloway.
    - Flying Solo: HRs, 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Flying Solo, 2002; 2 DATs (Audio 38)
      #20, 2002; Original Master 4/8/2002
    - Flying Solo. #20, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Flying Solo. #1, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Flying Solo. #2, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 196. Pennies From Heaven: The Lyrics of Johnny Burke, Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-
    Burke, Johnny, 1908-1964
    - Pennies From Heaven. #25, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Pennies From Heaven. #43, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Pennies From Heaven. #40, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 197. Emperor Norton's Hunch: The Yerba Buena Stompers Play Lu Watters, Yerba Buena Stompers.
    With guest the Yerba Buena Stompers.
    Watters, Lu
    - Emperor Norton's Hunch. #26, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Emperor Norton's Hunch. #26, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 198. Richard Rodgers 100th Birthday Bash, Ferro, Nina
    With guest Nina Ferro. Later renamed "I'll Take Manhattan: The Music of Richard Rodgers."
    Rodgers, Richard, 1902-1979
    - Richard Rodgers 100th Birthday Bash. #29, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Richard Rodgers 100th Birthday Bash. #29, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - I'll Take Manhattan: The Music of Richard Rodgers. #29, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - I'll Take Manhattan: The Music of Richard Rodgers. #41, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - I'll Take Manhattan: The Music of Richard Rodgers. #33, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 199. The Jim Cullum Jazz Band at 40
    - JCJB 40th Anniversary Greetings/Tags Master, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band at 40: Greetings/Tags; Hot Rhythm; Tunes for Consideration, 4 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band at 40. #30, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band at 40. #30, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 200. 42nd Street: Harry Warren and The Golden Age of Hollywood Musicals, Phillips, Russ, trombonist
    With guest Russ Phillips.
    Warren, Harry, 1893-1981; Musicals
    - 42nd Street. #36, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - 42nd Street. #23, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 201. The Rhythmakers: A Gathering of Jazz Titans, Baker, Clint; Heitger, Duke; Holt, David, 1946-
    With guests trumpeter Duke Heitger and guitarist Clint Baker.
    Rhythmakers.
    - Rhythmakers. #37, Safety, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Rhythmakers. #37, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Rhythmakers. #28, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Rhythmakers. #35, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Rhythmakers. #12, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Rhythmakers. #5, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 202. Miracles of Swing: The Legacy of Bunny Berigan and Other Swing Era Stars, Barnard, Bob
    With guest Bob Barnard. Record live at the Stanford Jazz Workshop. See also 2002 Stanford recordings.
    Berigan, Bunny, 1908-1942; Stanford Jazz Workshop.; Swing (Music)
    - Miracles of Swing, 2002; 2 DATs (Audio 38)
      #39 Final Mix Safety, 2002; #39 Credit Fixes 9/2002
    - Miracles of Swing. #39, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Miracles of Swing. #32, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 203. Bourbon Street "Top Ten:" The Jim Cullum Jazz Band in Concert, Barnard, Bob
    With guest Bob Barnard. Record at the Stanford Jazz Workshop. See also 2002 Stanford recordings.
    - RW #40 Bourbon Street Top 10 Script, 2002-08-15; 1 DAT (Audio 79)
    - Bourbon Street "Top Ten" #40, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Bourbon Street "Top Ten." #40, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Bourbon Street "Top Ten." #47, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Bourbon Street Top Ten. #45, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 204. A Night at the Movies with Irving Berlin, Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-
    Berlin, Irving, 1888-1989
    - Night at the Movies with Irving Berlin. #43, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Night at the Movies with Irving Berlin. #45, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Night at the Movies with Irving Berlin. #18, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 205. Swingin' on a Riff: The Legacy of the Benny Goodman Sextet, Allen, Harry, saxophonist; Vaché, Allan
    With guests Allan Vaché and Harry Allen.
    Benny Goodman Sextet.; Goodman, Benny, 1909-1986
    - Swinging on a Riff. #45, 2002; 1 DAT (Audio 38)
    - Swingin' on a Riff. #45, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Swinging on a Riff. #3, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Swinging on a Riff. #23, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Swingin' on a Riff. #41, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 206. Hot Rhythm on the River: A Look Back at 40 Years with The Jim Cullum Jazz Band
    - Show Disc, 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
    - Hot Rhythm on the River, 2002; 2 DATs (Audio 38)
      #46, 2002; Dup Master 2002
    - Hot Rhythm on the River. #46, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 207. Jazz Strings: A Tribute to Jazz Violinist Stephane Grappelli, Hot Club of San Francisco.
    With guest band the Hot Club of San Francisco.
    Grappelli, Steand#769;phane
    - Jazz Strings. #49, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Jazz Strings. #4, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Jazz Strings. #24, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 208. Home for the Holidays, Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Wilber, Bob
    With guests including Dick Hyman, Rebecca Kilgore and Bob Wilber.
    - Home for the Holidays: Rough Tracks, 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Home for the Holidays for RW 51/02, 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Home for the Holidays, 2002; 2 DATs (Audio 39)
      #51, 2002; Safety 2002
    - Home for the Holidays. #51, 2002; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Home for the Holidays: The Jim Cullum Jazz Band in Concert. #50, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Home for the Holidays. #51, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Home for the Holidays. #51, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Home for the Holidays. #51, 2009; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 209. Trombone Madness: From Kid Ory's New Orleans to Miff Mole's New York Sessions, Havens, Bob; Phillips, Russ, trombonist; Pittsley, Mike
    With guest trombonists Mike Pittsley, Russ Phillips, and Bob Havens.
    Mole, Miff, 1898-1961; Ory, Kid, 1886-1973
    - Trombone Madness. #2, 2003; 1 DAT (Audio 39)
    - Trombone Madness. #2, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Trombone Madness. #8, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 210. Jivin' at the Stage Door Canteen: A 1940s Revue, Gibson, Banu; Havens, Bob; Phillips, Russ, trombonist; Pittsley, Mike
    With guests Banu Gibson, Russ Phillips, Mike Pittsley, and Bob Havens.
    - Jivin' at the Stage Door Canteen, 2003; 2 DATs (Audio 39)
      #4, 2003 [note: cover indicates #4 is Jelly Roll Blues, label says Hollywood Canteen"]; #5, 2003
    - Jivin' at the Stage Door Canteen. #5, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Jivin' at the Stage Door Canteen. #49, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 211. Landmarks of Jazz: The Music, The Musicians, and The Memories, Barnard, Bob; Gordon, Bobby; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Oakley, Leon; Pizzarelli, Bucky; Pizzarelli, John; Walbridge, Mike
    with guests Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, Dick Hyman, Bobby Gordon, John Pizzarelli, Bucky Pizzarelli, and Bob Barnard.
    - Landmarks of Jazz Promos, 2002-12-23; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 88)
    - Landmarks of Jazz. #8, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 212. Davenport Blues: The Bix Beiderbecke Letters, Bridgett, Darren
    Letters read by actor David Bridgett.
    - RW #12. Bix Letters Home, KQED. Darren Bridgett Reading Scripts, 2003-02-07; 1 DAT (Audio 79)
    - Bix Letters David Script, 2003-02-28; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Bix Beiderbecke Letter Reading by Max Cowan, 2003-01-27; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Davenport Blues: Rough Tracks, 3 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Mission Pharmacal-Citircal Presents Davenport Blues: The Bix Beiderbecke Letters, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Davenport Blues. #12, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Davenport Blues. #35, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Davenport Blues. #53, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Davenport Blues. #11, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Davenport Blues. #45, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 213. Bumpy Beds and Broken-down Buses: On the Road in the 30s, Cheatham, Doc; Hampton, Lionel; Hinton, Milt; Terry, Clark
    with Milt Hinton, Doc Cheatham, Lionel Hampton, and Clark Terry. Title changed in 2005 to "Milt, Clark and Doc: On the Road in the 30s and40s."
    - Bumpy Beds and Broken-down Buses: Production Pieces; Tunes, 2005; 3 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Bumpy Beds and Broken-down Buses. #13, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Milt, Clark and Doc: On the Road in the 30s and40s. #26, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Milt, Clark and Doc: On the Road in the 30s and40s. #5, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 214. Jazz Legends Play the Blues: A Salute to the Year of the Blues 2003, Baker, Clint; Heitger, Duke; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; McShann, Jay; Mehling, Paul; Terry, Clark; Warfield, William; Wilber, Bob; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Joe Williams, Clark Terry, William Warfield, Dick Hyman, Paul Mehling, Duke Heitger, Bob Wilber, Clint Baker, and Jay McShann.
    - Legends - Blues Rough Show, 2003-03-05; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
    - Jazz Legends Play the Blues. #15, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Jazz Legends Play the Blues. #36, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Jazz Legends Play the Blues: Boogie Woogie to KC Blues. #47, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 215. Spring Fever: A Riverwalk Jazz Celebration, Ferro, Nina; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Oakley, Leon
    With guests Dick Hyman, Rebecca Kilgore, Nina Ferro, and Leon Oakley.
    - Spring Fever. #17, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Spring Fever. #13, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 216. Heart and Soul: Bessie, Billie and The Blues, Baker, Clint; Heitger, Duke; Hopkins, Linda, 1924-; Woods, Carol
    With guests Linda Hopkins, Carol Woods, Duke Heitger, and Clint Baker. 2006 rebroadcast titled "Bessie, Billie, and the Blues."
    Holiday, Billie, 1915-1959; Smith, Bessie, 1894-1937
    - Heart and Soul: First Mix, 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Heart and Soul. #21, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Bessie, Billie and The Blues. #12, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Bessie, Billie and The Blues. #9, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 217. Flow Gently, Sweet Rhythm: The Maxine Sullivan Story, Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Sheridan, John, pianist
    With guests Rebecca Kilgore and John Sheridan. Recorded at the Sacramento Jazz Jubilee. See also 2003 Sacramento recordings. 2003 broadcast titled "Maxine Sullivan: A Life In Jazz." 2011 version broadcast as "Flow Gently Sweet Rhythm: Maxine Sullivan at 100" (#374.)
    Sullivan, Maxine, 1911-1987
    - Maxine Sullivan: Edits; Archive, 2003; 4 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Flow Gently, Sweet Rhythm: The Maxine Sullivan Story. #25, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Maxine Sullivan: A Life In Jazz. #49, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Flow Gently, Sweet Rhythm: The Maxine Sullivan Story. #15, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Flow Gently, Sweet Rhythm: The Maxine Sullivan Story. #23, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 218. Bix and His Gang: A Birthday Jam, Giordano, Vince
    With guest Vince Giordano. 2006 broadcast shortened title to "Bix and His Gang."
    - Bix and His Gang. #26, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Bix and His Gang. #23, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Bix and His Gang. #17, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 219. Hot Jazz for a Summer Day: A Backyard Jazz Festival, Allred, Bill; Higgins, Eddie, 1932-; Independence Hall Jazz Band.; Kellso, Jon-Erik; Saunders, Tom, cornet player; Smith, Hal, drummer; Tommy Saunders Midwest All Stars.
    With special guests the Independence Hall Jazz Band, Eddie Higgins, the Tommy Saunders Midwest All-Stars, Hal Smith, Jon-Erik Kellso, and Bill Allred. Also titled "At The Jazz Band BBQ: Hot Jazz for a Summer Day."
    - Hot Jazz for a Summer Day. #29, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - At The Jazz Band BBQ: Hot Jazz for a Summer Day. #30, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 220. Hot Jazz from the Big Easy to the Windy City: The New Black Eagle Jazz Band Live, New Black Eagle Jazz Band.
    With guest band the New Black Eagle Jazz Band.
    - Hot Jazz from the Big Easy to the Windy City: New Black Eagle Jazz Band, 2003-06-30; 1 CD-R (Audio 100)
    - Hot Jazz from the Big Easy to the Windy City. #31, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 221. Get Ready for B.E.D.: A Jim Cullum Jazz Band Concert with Guest Band B.E.D., B.E.D. (Musical group).; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Rebecca Kilgore Quartet.
    With guest band B.E.D. (now known as the Rebecca Kilgore Quartet).
    - Get Ready for B.E.D. #34, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 222. Hot Chamber Jazz: The Benny Goodman Trio 1935-1954, Hedges, Chuck; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-; Sheridan, John, pianist; Vaché, Allan
    With guests John Sheridan, Rebecca Kilgore, Allan Vaché, and Chuck Hedges.
    Benny Goodman Trio.; Goodman, Benny, 1909-1986
    - Hot Chamber Jazz: Edits, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Hot Chamber Jazz. #36, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Hot Chamber Jazz. #15, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Hot Chamber Jazz. #8, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 223. Flock O' Blues: The Rare Gems of Bix Beiderbecke, Giordano, Vince
    With guest Vince Giordano.
    - Flock O' Blues. #37, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Flock O' Blues. #35, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Flock O' Blues. #4, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 224. Swing That Music: Memories and Stories of Louis Armstrong, Bagneris, Vernel
    With guest Vernel Bagneris. Live from the Stanford Jazz Workshop. See also 2003 Stanford recordings.
    Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971; Stanford Jazz Workshop.
    - Swing That Music: Memories and Stories of Louis Armstrong. Rough Edits, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 87)
    - Swing That Music: Memories and Stories of Louis Armstrong. #40, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Swing That Music: Memories and Stories of Louis Armstrong. #14, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Swing That Music: Memories and Stories of Louis Armstrong. #47, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Swing That Music: Memories and Stories of Louis Armstrong. #31, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 225. Wild Man Blues: The Eccentric Genius of Jelly Roll Morton, Bagneris, Vernel
    - Wild Man Blues. #42, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Wild Man Blues. #19, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Wild Man Blues. #28, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Wild Man Blues. #40, 2011; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 226. Fletcher Henderson and Don Redman: The Birth of the Big Band Reed Section, Cusack, Kim; Vaché, Allan
    Henderson, Fletcher, 1897-1952; Redman, Don
    - Henderson/Redman, 2003-04; 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Fletcher Henderson and Don Redman. #44, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
    - Fletcher Henderson and Don Redman. #20, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Fletcher Henderson and Don Redman. #22, 2006; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Fletcher Henderson and Don Redman. #7, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 227. Zoot and Al: The Brotherhood of Prez, Allen, Harry, saxophonist
    With guest Harry Allen.
    Cohn, Al; Sims, Zoot
    - Zoot and Al. #46, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Zoot and Al. #22, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Zoot and Al. #2, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Zoot and Al. #35, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 228. Piano Man: An Earl Hines Centennial Celebration, Bagneris, Vernel; Cusack, Kim; Gordon, Bobby; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Sheridan, John, pianist
    With guests Dick Hyman, John Sheridan, Kim Cusack, Bobby Gordon, and Vernel Bagneris. Later title: "Piano Man: Earl Hines, The Father of Modern Jazz Piano."
    - Piano Man. #51, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Piano Man: Earl Hines, The Father of Modern Jazz Piano. #43, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Piano Man: Earl Hines, The Father of Modern Jazz Piano. #48, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 229. Milestones of American Jazz Masters, Carter, Benny; Giordano, Vince; Grosz, Marty; Hopkins, Linda, 1924-; Stein, Andy; Williams, Joe, 1918-1999
    With guests Linda Hopkins, Joe Williams, Andy Stein, Marty Grosz, Vince Giordano, and Benny Carter.
    - Milestones of American Music Masters: Mix 1: Reference Track CD, 2003; 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Milestones of American Music Masters. #52, 2003; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 230. Red Lights and Hot Nights: The Last Days of Storyville, Bagneris, Vernel
    - Red Lights and Hot Nights: Production Pieces; Hot Tamale Man, 2 CD-Rs (Audio 100)
    - Red Lights and Hot Nights. #2, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Red Lights and Hot Nights. #1, 2005; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Red Lights and Hot Nights. #49, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
  - 231. Manhattan After Dark: The Night Club Scene in the 1920s, Bagneris, Vernel
    - Manhattan After Dark. #5, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Manhattan After Dark. #41, 2004; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
    - Manhattan After Dark. #13, 2007; 1 CD-R (Audio 132)
  - 232. Love, Hollywood Style: Romance and the Silver Screen, Ferro, Nina; Kilgore, Rebecca, 1948-